You could choose a custom frame, but you also have the choice of doing a ready made frame.
We sell this custom frame here.
It's like, fifty dollars a foot.
We've made a ready made out of this same molding because I did a large picture in this for my customer and I had a little bit left over.
So, this particular ready made is an eleven by fourteen and it regularly sells for three hundred and thirty five dollars.
But with already mades, we cut the price almost in half.
So, this ready made is one hundred and sixty eight.
Or, you have this same one...this is an eleven by fourteen (the same size) and it only runs thirty three dollars.
So, you can see how there is a huge difference between the price in one and the other.
We have this picture of a little kitty.
Everyone loves their animals, their cats and their dogs.
So, we choose which size we want to frame this in.
We might choose an eleven by fourteen and it fits in that really nicely.
But, we might choose a sixteen by twenty.
See?
That leaves a little bit more matting around it.
So then, what we want to do is we'll pick the matting that goes with it.
So, for me, I've picked these two colors that I think would go very nicely with this picture.
So you can take a simple picture of your cat or your dog or your children and make an absolutely gorgeous frame for it.